gamentio.com 2019-04-06

# gamentioPP - gamentio

## PRIVACY POLICY

This privacy policy forms part of our Website's Terms of Use Agreement. By accepting the Terms of Use Agreement and the Privacy Policy on the registration page, you consent to provide sensitive personal data or personal information and are aware of the purpose of sharing such information. Please do not register if you do not wish to share the mandatory personal information with Logic Simplified Pvt. Ltd. on their website www.gamentio.com (hereinafter referred as "Gamentio") requested at the time of registration. Registration procedure cannot be completed until information in the non-optional/mandatory fields is provided. Certain additional personal information may be requested by Gamentio for permitting you access to any Tournaments/Contests/Play with real money games organized by Gamentio.

## 1\. Policy objective:

**1.1** Gamentio respects your privacy and assures you that any information provided by you to Gamentio is protected and will be dealt with according to this Privacy Policy and the applicable laws. To avail the services offered on www.gamentio.com, you may have to provide certain information to us. This Policy provides the procedure followed by Gamentio to gather, use, store, disclose and manage users' personal data. Gamentio only collects personal data for the purpose of verifying user accounts, maintaining the accounts of the users, completing transactions of the users and for analyzing user behavior and requirements.

## 2\. What is included in personal data?

**2.1** User's personal data includes the following types of data or information:

  1. Sensitive Personal Data: 
    * Account password
    * Financial information such as Bank account or credit card or debit card or other payment instrument details
  2. Other Personal Information: 
    * Name
    * Date of birth
    * Telephone number
    * Postal/Contact address
    * Your PAN or your Guardian's PAN (as applicable)
    * Guardian's Personal Details
    * Aadhaar Card details to verify relationship with Guardian.
    * Passport details to verify relationship with Guardian.
    * The IP address of your computer, browser type and language.
    * The date and the time during which you accessed the site.
    * The address of the website which you may have used to link to the Website
    * Your photograph for testimonials and other promotions.
    * Such other information that is defined as sensitive personal data or information in law.

## 3\. User Consents:

**3.1 Consent for use of Sensitive Personal Data and Other Personal Information:**

**3.1.1** All users of Gamentio consent to the use of Sensitive Personal Data and Other Personal Information for the purpose stated in this policy. We restrict access of personal information to our employees, contractors and agents and only allow access to those who need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf. 

**3.1.2** By using our website, it is understood that you have given your consent to the collection and use of Sensitive Personal Data and Other Personal Information by Gamentio.com and its partners and affiliates.

**3.1.3** Photographs once provided by you for marketing purposes gives Gamentio irrevocable rights to use it and it is completely Gamentio's discretion to delete or not use it any further.

**3.1.4** In order to play âGamentio Coinsâ games, you may be required to make online payments. To process such financial transactions, we may use third-party electronic payment processors or service providers (ESPs). By accepting this Privacy Policy, You expressly consent to Personal Information necessary for the processing of transactions being shared with ESPs. We take steps to ensure that our arrangements with ESPs protect your privacy.

**3.1.5** Gamentio may also use software applications for website traffic analysis and to gather statistics, used for advertising and for determining the efficacy and popularity of Gamentio among others.

**3.1.6** We reserve the right to conduct a security review at any time to validate Your identity, age, the registration data provided by You and to verify Your use of the Services and Your financial transactions for potential breach of the Terms of Use Agreement and of any applicable law. By using our website, you authorize Us, Our staff, agents and suppliers to use Your Personal Information and to disclose Your Personal Information to third parties for the purposes of validating the information you provide to us.

**3.1.7** By filling your mobile number on our site, you are giving Logic Simplified Pvt. Ltd. the right to contact you by Call/SMS to provide you information on all promotional activity/events conducted by Gamentio and its partners. Your mobile number will not be used for any third party communication whatsoever.

**3.1.8** Presently, Gamentio is using display advertising and remarketing through Google Analytics, wherein third party vendors including Google, display our ads on sites across the internet and uses first party cookies and third party cookies together to inform, optimize and serve ads based on visits of visitors to our website. Our visitors are free to opt out of Google Analytics for display advertising and customize Google display network ads using ads preference manager.

**3.1.9** Users are entitled to withdraw consent for use of their Sensitive Personal Data or Other Personal Information by emailing a specific request to support@gamentio.com. Withdrawal of consent of all or any part of Sensitive Personal Data and Other Personal Information may result in immediate withdrawal of any right to avail the services provided by Gamentio. Withdrawal of consent shall not restrict the right of Gamentio to use Other Personal Information for analysis of user data, subject to the condition that the Other Personal Information used in any analysis is not personally identifiable to any individual user. 

## 3.2 Consent to use of Cookies:

**3.2.1** A cookie is a small text file that uniquely identifies your browser. You understand that when you visit the Website, cookies may be left in your computer. The cookies assigned by the servers of Gamentio may be used to personalize your experience on the Website. Additionally, cookies may also be used for authentication, game management, data analysis and security purposes.

**3.2.2** Cookies may also be assigned by the advertisers of Gamentio when you click on any of the advertisements which may be displayed on the Website in which case such cookies are controlled by these advertisers and not Gamentio.

## 3.3 Consent to use Anti-Cheating Software

**3.3.1** Our software package contains certain features designed to detect use of automated programs that enable artificial (non-human) intelligence to play on our site. Use of such 'bot' software programs violates the Terms of Use Agreement, where we deem it detrimental to other players. By installing Our software and using the Services, You consent to Our software performing the functions described in this section. Our software may perform any or all of the following functions in order to detect the use of illicit automated programs and ensure that We maintain a 'cheat free' environment for all users: 

  * Scan your list of active software applications while you are using the services;
  * Scan your list of active processes while you are using the services; and
  * Scan the files in your services and site-related program folders to ensure that only 'non-hacked' versions of Our software are being used. If any of the foregoing processes reveals a suspect application or process, Our software may scan the files associated with the suspect application or process and compile a composite mesh (i.e., a profile that characterizes the files associated with the application or process) to be matched against profiles for known illicit automated programs. Our software will not perform any random search of large portions of Your hard drive, equipment or files, and it will not transmit any information to Us or to any third party other than the information you provide to us.

## 3.4 Consent to email communication: 

**3.4.1** When you register your email address with Gamentio, you agree to receive email communication from Gamentio, entities specifically authorized by Gamentio and other users. You also agree and acknowledge that when you use our referral program for referring someone, Gamentio will send emails to such person referred by you on your behalf and the email headers will carry your email address as the address from which such emails are sent.

## 4\. Data Security:

**4.1** We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. Gamentio has a comprehensive information security program and information security policies which contain managerial, technical, operational and physical security control measures adopted by Gamentio for the protection of Sensitive Personal Data and Other Personal Information.

**4.2** Information gathered by Gamentio is stored securely using several information security applications including firewalls. However, security is always relative and Gamentio cannot guarantee that its security measures are absolute and cannot be breached. Data which is transmitted over the Internet is inherently exposed to security risks or threats. For instance, information transmitted via chat or email can be compromised and used by others. Therefore, Gamentio cannot guarantee any security for such information in the course of transmission through the internet infrastructure or any unsolicited disclosures made by any user availing the services of the Website.

**4.3** When you register with Gamentio, your account is protected by means of login information which includes a username and a password that is known only to you. Therefore, you should not provide your personal information to anyone whosoever and breach hereof constitutes violation of this Policy and can also result in closure of account in certain cases. If you become aware of or reasonably suspect any breach of security, including compromise of your login information, it is your responsibility to immediately notify Gamentio.

**4.4** The Website may contain links to other websites. Such websites are governed by their own privacy policies and Gamentio does not exercise any control over them. It is your responsibility to read and understand the privacy policy of such websites when you follow a link outside www.gamentio.com. You are advised to exercise caution in sharing any personal information with any third party that advertises on the Website, and Gamentio shall not be responsible for such information provided by you on third party websites.

**4.5** Gamentio has a policy of not sharing any personally identifiable information with anyone other than entities specifically authorized by Gamentio which may include advertisers and sponsors of Gamentio. However, Gamentio may use your name, photo, Login ID and the state from where you are participating when announcing the results of any contests run on the Website. Such contests are further governed by terms and conditions specific to such contests which shall be available on the website as and when such a contest is run on the website. Gamentio conducts periodic analysis and survey of the traffic to www.gamentio.com for market research and advertising purposes. Gamentio reserves the right to share your registration information with Gamentio appointed market research and advertising companies or firms from time to time for the said purposes. Gamentio may also use cumulative non-personal information for auditing and analysis purposes with the aim of improving its services.

## 5\. Exclusions:

**5.1** Gamentio may share Sensitive Personal Data and Other Personal Information if sharing of such information is necessary:

  1. in compliance with legal processes or Government directives;
  2. to enforce the Terms of Use Agreement and/or this Privacy Policy;
  3. for prevention of fraud;
  4. for issues involving information security,
  5. to protect:
    * your rights;
    * rights of Gamentio; and
    * rights of the general public.

## 6\. Mergers and Other Events Requiring Tranfer of Information:

**6.1** If we should ever file for bankruptcy, or become insolvent, or be acquired by a third party, merge with a third party, sell all or part of Our assets, or transfer substantially all or part of Our relevant assets to a third party, We are entitled to share the Personal Information and all other information You have provided through the Services to potential and subsequent business and merger partners.

## 7\. Protection of Children

**7.1** The Services are not intended for or directed at persons under the age of Thirteen (13) years. Any person who informs us that his age is thirteen (13) years or above, it is our policy to uncover the services which may require us to access and verify the person's Personal Information. If we become aware that a minor has attempted to or has submitted personal information via the Services, We will not accept this information and will take steps to remove such information from our records in a secure manner.

## 8\. Limitation of Liability:

**8.1** Gamentio confirms that this Privacy Policy is only a description of its operation regarding user information. This Policy is not intended to and does not create any legal rights in your favour or in the favour of any other person. Gamentio reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time without giving you prior notice. The liability of Gamentio shall be limited to removal of Sensitive Personal Data from the system of the Website and removal of personally identifiable elements of the Other Personal Information. Notwithstanding anything to the contrary contained in this Privacy Policy and elsewhere, the aggregate liability of Gamentio for all claims for damages pursuant to provisions of services on the Website, including claims in respect to the violation of this Policy, shall be limited to the aggregate maximum as provided in the Terms of Use Agreement.

## 9\. Grievance Officer:

**9.1** All complaints relating to personal data must be sent to the Grievance Officer at support@gamentio.com.
